{
    "subject": "resource/Oliver_Parker",
    "predicate": "property/shortDescription",
    "object": "British film director and screenwriter",
    "human_readable": "Oliver Parker is a British film director and screenwriter.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9288038611412048,
            "question": "Name some films directed by Oliver Parker."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9023851156234741,
            "question": "Is Oliver Parker involved in writing for films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8999235033988953,
            "question": "Is Oliver Parker British?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.723860502243042,
            "question": "Has Oliver Parker worked in the film industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6276986002922058,
            "question": "Besides directing, what else is Oliver Parker known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5899808406829834,
            "question": "What kind of films does Oliver Parker direct?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5860782265663147,
            "question": "What does Oliver Parker do?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5549172759056091,
            "question": "What nationality is Oliver Parker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5350944399833679,
            "question": "What is Oliver Parker's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32575955986976624,
            "question": "What is Oliver Parker's background in the arts?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Oliver Parker is a British film director and screenwriter.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5848_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Oliver Parker's profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5848_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What nationality is Oliver Parker?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5848_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What does Oliver Parker do?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5848_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5848_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5848_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5848_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5848_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5848_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5848_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5848_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5848_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5848_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5848_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Oliver Parker is a British film director and screenwriter\" based on the provided context information:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThis is because all five documents provide information that confirms Oliver Parker's nationality as British, his profession as a film director, and his work as a screenwriter."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Oliver Parker is a British film director and screenwriter.\" Multiple documents, including those with file paths /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5848/re-ranker-msmarco/2.txt, /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5848/re-ranker-msmarco/101.txt, and /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5848/re-ranker-msmarco/22.txt, confirm Oliver Parker's roles as a British film director and screenwriter."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}